Piotr Górski

Shortly before graduating i decided to change careers. Since 2022 i've been mostly focused on expanding my Web Development knowledge, but also trying to learn more about general Computer Science topics. I'm confident in my UI/UX and graphic design skills.













Mail: hello@piotrgorski.com

Location: Poznań

I'm good at:

Skills

Frontend • HTML CSS/SCSS • JavaScript TypeScript • React.js

Tel: +48 000 000 000

I have worked with:

Backend • Node.js
NextJS • Vue 3 • Redux
PostgreSQL • MongoDB
Redis • FireBase
GraphQL • REST API
Chakra • MUI • i18next
Webpack • WordPress
Git • Figma • Photoshop

Integrity • Curiosity Communication

Languages

soft:

English - **B2**German - **A1**Polish - **Native**

Hobbies

Volleyball • Gym Graphic Design 3D Modelling

Experience

June 2023 - currently

HTML Email Developer - Anspert 3D studio.

- Creating and testing HTML newsletters/signatures
- Designing and implementing responsive layouts
- Working in multilayered business structure

Developing commercial Fullstack Application for alpine festival organization, with my mentor. (more information below, under 'Projects')

September 2020 - July 2021

Architects Assistant - Arte Monoblok Architekci.

- Created concept projects and visualizations
- Did technical drawings with CAD/BIM software and initial sketches in the field
- Worked directly with clients and partner industries
- Used softwares such as: AutoCAD, ArchiCAD, Lumion, Blender, SketchUp, Photoshop

Education

Poznań University of Technology - Architecture.

February 2020 - September 2021 - Master's 4,65 GPA

October 2016 - February 2020 - Engineer's

Projects

Specific information about every project can be found after clicking related image.

Alpine Festival



x-com Clone



Musicalia



ALpost



I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).